You managed to cover yourself...
...in Conqueror's Haki...
But the way you handled it..
...was crude and clumsy.
Gum-Gum...
Still trying to win against me?
Oh, I'm enjoying this!
What was it, now...?
TO
You couldn't be Joyboy either...
..I guess...
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
ww
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
rhythmZome Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
I'm doing this for myself,
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
So forge ahead, and draw your own map as you go!
Edited by fedew Subtitles by HatSubs
Raccoon dog...
Take this!
He grabbed his head!
11 111
Chopperemon-san is overpowering Queen..!
Amazing!
You sure sound ragged for someone who's supposed to be winning!
Right, Raccoon Dog?
Wonder how much more he can take.
Miem!
Castle interior Third floor
We shall no longer take flight nor hide!
There you are, Young Master Yamato! Come back to us, nice and easy!
That's...
Momonosuke!
Huh?
The young master's not handcuffed!
Indeed! / I am no longer a captive!
I am...
...Oden!
First floor Crawl space
Shinobu.
Aye?
I believe.. I cannot and must not perish.
That goes without saying! Why do you say this now?!
Who is it?!
Eh?! What is it this time?!
Ring, ring, ring.. Ring, ring, ring...
Clik.
Kaido-sama! We found Momonosuke!
Be right there.
Ayyyye!
Let all of Onigashima know, Bao Huang...
My battle with Straw Hat is over.
No matter what they do now, it's all pointless.
More incoming! It's another candy arrow volley!
Take cover!
Chopperemon-san!
The Rumble Ball's effects wear off in less than ten minutes...
Lot of good that extra time did me...!
Those are laughable results!
Three minutes of gigantification?
What is it you think you can do in that time?
But there's a side effect of remaining in monster form for more than three minutes..
So what?!
You only care about yourself, then?!
And you call yourself a pirate!
Come again?!
I dictate the chemicals, and you fetch them!
We will be extending the duration of gigantification to thirty minutes!
Ten times the length!
There will be risks, oh yes...
...but you're not afraid, are you?
Of course not!
I'm a pirate!
Black Light Roast!
JQUEEN
Scurrying around..
M NN
Shaddap!
11 Ya cocky little raccoon dog!
Marys:
Spread-the-News Mode!
To all those here at Onigashima, may I have your attention, pleeeease!
The duel iiiis... over!
The highest bounty among the enemy forces, Straw Hat Luffy, waaaas...
....de-fea-teeed!
Wha?!
Chopperemon-san!
Straw Hat!
It's over, then...
Kaido-sama choked the life out of hiim...
Ya hear that?
BF
F Ain't no way!
...and sent Straw Hat Luffy to the deepest, darkest depths of the sea!
Good news!
Did you hear?
I couldn't care less about that dumbass!
Both the Kozuki samuraaaai..
...and the captaaaaaain.
...have fallen!
Who's next? Can anyone win?!
Even Kin'emon's party?!
Big Bro Luffy!
Kaido-sama's heading downstairs to start "cleeeeaning" house!
Can't believe she wrecked the castle... Dammit, Linlin!
Kaido-sama will... gladly accept your surrender!
**
Any that raise their hands in surrender.. and submit to uuuus...
...will be spared and welcomeeeed... as subordinaaaates!
Whatta load of bull!
Momonosuke-sama! What is wrong?!
Kin'emon!
I am here!
I must tell everyone!
Surrender, sub-jects of Wa-no!
The war is loooost!
The contest has endeeeed!
Straw Hat Luffy was...
...sent to the deepest, darkest depths of the seeeea!
Is this not one of the Marys?! Its presence here must mean...
...our situation is dire, is it not, Kin-sama?!
I have had it!
Hey! Heeey!
That voice..!
Momonosuke!
How long it has been!
What... It cannot be!
You look to be well too, Shinobu!
F-Father!
You mustn't, Shinobu-san!
Father! Father!
Do not set eyes upon him!
Eh?!
Father!
What is this? Let him go!
This is the tearful reunion of father and son!
It is no such thing!
Stand back, Shinobu!
Huh?!
I am Kozuki Oden!
Once before, and now again!
Spouting your obvious lies!
Come now, Kiku, what is the matter?! No need for the grim face!
Tis !
Silence!
podocoodHow dare you...
...do what you did to Ashura-san..
Do not approach, Kiku! What is it you intend?
You will not utter my name wearing that countenance...
Kanjuro!
Ho, now, Kiku! Surely you jest!
I took you and lzo under my wing...
So, you two...
Where are your parents?
Do you have the will to cut me down?
I haven't the will...
Kin-sama... I cannot...
Kanjuro!
Kiku!
Thanks to the wound you inflicted upon me..
I, too, am at death's door, Kiku!
Kiku!
Kin-sama...
My shame is unbearable..
I, Kikunojo of the Fallen Snow...
...can go no further...
However...
...if the fallen snow melts..
...surely this country's Dawn is soon to come.
EV Foolishness!
It shall come!
And the light from Wano's Dawn shall stretch into the afterlife!
Kikunojo!
Were this a stage production,
it would certainly have been hailed as this century's greatest work!
And you are the next actor in line, Kin!
I shall set the stage for your final moments!
A most unfortunate man... His lord, slain... A friend, now turned foe...
And now, one of his comrades-in-arms, lost forever...
What awaits him?
Tragedy, perhaps?!
Or comedy?!
Play your role, Kin'emon!
Decorate this stage with your honorable death!
Kanjuro!
That's it!
Please wait!
Are you gonna take in a pervert like him, Oden-san?!
Just let me off! How many times do I need to say sorry?!
Indeed! Raizo moves with the same rhythm.
I believe he has this kind of power..
Ninja Art: Blindfold Technique!
Guess who!
C-Could it be you, Kanjuro? I know you are the only person there..
Look out! Duck!
Stop this ridiculous "ninja art" nonse
If there is anyone that ought drop the curtain upon my play,
it should be you!
Because upon this stage...
We were... the best of... friends...
Kiku! Kiku!
K-Kaido!
So you were hiding here, runt!
Shinobu! Take Momonosuke-sama and flee!
A-Aye!
Out of my way, Wano Samurai!
I will not allow you to pass!
Then kiss your ass goodbye!
Kin'emoooon!
Luffy!
Luffy... Did you really lose?
Then... What do we...
What do we do?!
Luffy!
Straw Hat lost?!
There's no point in fighting anymore?!
Bao Huang's announcement.
..caused great distress among the samurai united by their desire to subdue Kaido.
The straw hat man?! Impossible...!
What of Momonosuke-sama's state?!
.. Luffy wouldn't go down that easily! +
Yeah, hear that?! Don't underestimate our captain! *
And so, the airborne Onigashima..
...finally reaches the skies over the mainland of Wano.
After chowing down on that dumpling from Speed, I feel freakin' amazing!
Dr:S I dunno the particulars,
but the bunch of ya managed to rope in the strongest rookies imaginable!
They ain't weak! 1111
It's just that Kaido-sama's...
...too strong!
Slicing Rounds!
Kappa Style:
RIVER OF RETRIBUTION River of Retribution!
Even if Straw Hat is dead, we do not give up the fight 'til Kaido is defeated!
But...
We have yet to confirm whether Straw Hat is alive or dead!
But even hinting at his death is enough to crush morale...
Aye... We've no way to uncover the truth!
I swear, every last one of ya..
//1 Don't even think about losing!
Luffy...
No crying...
You just gotta fight, 'n fight some more...
W Raccoon Dog-san! N
WM You had spunk, so I felt like messin' with ya a little!
Your top man goes down, and now all hell's broken loose!
And now, a present from me to the unruly mob.
Mlem!
Not that attack again!
Candy Shower Apocalypse!
That's it; I can't take it anymore! I got nowhere to run!
You're toast, too, ya cowardly freak!
Bet your meat's real tender!
Diable Jambe...
...Rotisserie...
...SStrike!
There's just no way!
Hey.. Hey, hey, C'moooon!
Wait a damn minute!
Mleeeem!
Sanji!
Way to hang in there, Chopper.
Lu... Luffy's...
No crying allowed, dummy.
But..!
How many times have we seen...
...miracles?
Dammit all!
This is all yours.
Huh? Whoa!
What? Sanji! What's this?
Once he recovers, The'll be as strong as ten men.
You mean-two thousand men!
Hoeh?! Zoro?!
You just leave the dino to me!
Are you the one that did it?!
Judge's son!
He's not quitting the fight.
His captain's dead... Why does he keep fighting?
That's why I like you guys, oh yeah...
Wait...
-/11
Wait!
Wait..!
You are still. ••
...battling...
...me!
...dme!
And I will not...
...allow you to...
...lay even a finger..
..upon Momonosuke-sama!
1/111
Momonosuke-sama...
If I may humbly suggest...
From this day forth, refer to me...
..as your father!
of Kozuki Momo HH
Refer to you, Kin'emon, as "Father?"
That is correct!
I do not wish...
I do not wish for them to discover that you are descended from Oden-sama!
It would come as no surprise were an attempt were made on your life!
1 beg your understanding!
Very well. I am in your hands, Kin'emon...
Our thanks, Momonosuke-sama!
Now, refer to me as "Father," Momonosuke-sama!
That I shall, Kin'emon!
Using honorifics, referring to Kin'emon by name. Nothing at all has changed between you two!
You both certainly have a long road ahead of you!
Momonosuke, Momonosuke, Momonosuke...
...Sama.
...sama.
Momonosuke! Momonosuke! Momonosuke...
...Sama.
Momonosuke, Momonosuke, Momonosuke...
Momonosuke! Momonosuke! Momonosuke..
..Sama.
You have been uttering honorifics under your breath the entire time...
You have not improved a whit!
Mo... Mo...
Oh, this is a true ordeal!
Pull yourself together, Kin...
F-Father...
Perhaps I ought to trade places with you!
Father!
That was repugnant, no matter how you look at it!
Momonosuke!
What's the point of stalling for time?
What's gonna change by him fleeing?
Run, Shinobu!
Flee for your life, Momonosuke-sama!
Momonosuke!
Father!
You must live on!
Kaido!
Face death as a warrior should!
The problem with defeat is...
...few can accept it when it comes for them!
Eh? A frog?
Momonosuke-sama! Why?!
I must tell them...
I can hear his voice...
Luffy's voice!
Momo!
Luffy?
/ Momo!
Tell 'em!
My name is...
...Kozuki Momonosuke!
That's gotta be...
Momonosuke-sama! You're all right!
I shall relay to you...
...Luffy's words!
Is he crying?
But didn't Kaido kill Luffytaro?
Luffy yet lives!
He speaks to me now! Saying that he shall return!
And so...!
And so you must continue the fight!
^ Though it may be painful and difficult!
I must ask you...
As long as you draw breath, fight!
Well, if Momonosuke-sama's ordering it...
We fight while we still live!
11111 Mm-hmm!
Momo!
Tell 'em!
I promise ya, I'm gonna...
...beat Kaido!
CUNTINUED